A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Catalogs, Scientific and Educational Programs FA916
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Catalogs, Scientific and Educational Programs
1979-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA916
1.32 Cubic Feet 3 boxes.
3 boxes.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 419-1
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Scope and Contents
Consists of the Rockefeller University publication created to replace the Annual Report and Catalogue. This guide to the university outlines the history and structure of the institution, its graduate and postgraduate programs, as well as the scientific agendas of its laboratories.
Medical research; Operations management; Life sciences; Medical education; Biology -- Research; Medical sciences; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Rockefeller Foundation; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Rockefeller, John D. (John Davison); Rockefeller University; Greene, Jerome D.
- 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)